A Guide to the R. Bruce Merrifield papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA415
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Laboratory Files, 4
  - Notes and Notebooks
    - Merrifield, No. 310, February 1955 (Box 215, Folder 1377)
    - Merrifield, No. 311, "Peptide Synthesis," 1955 (Box 215, Folder 1378)
    - Merrifield, No. 312, July 1956 (Box 215, Folder 1379)
    - Merrifield, No. 313, February 1957 (Box 215, Folder 1380)
    - Merrifield, No. 314, July 1957 (Box 215, Folder 1381)
    - Merrifield, No. 315, "Thiamin Problem," 1957 (Box 215, Folder 1382)
    - Merrifield, No. 316, October 1957 (Box 215, Folder 1383)
    - Merrifield, No. 317, January 1958 (Box 216, Folder 1384)
    - Merrifield, No. 318, August 1958 (Box 216, Folder 1385)
    - Merrifield, No. 319, November 1958 (Box 216, Folder 1386)
    - Merrifield, No. 320, December 1958 (Box 216, Folder 1387)
    - Merrifield, No. 322, January 1960 (Box 216, Folder 1388)
    - Merrifield, No. 323, June 1960 (Box 216, Folder 1389)
    - Merrifield, No. 324, December 1960 (Box 216, Folder 1390)
    - Merrifield, No. 325, June 1961 (Box 216, Folder 1391)
    - Merrifield, No. 326, February 1962 (Box 217, Folder 1392)
    - Merrifield, No. 327, October 1962 (Box 217, Folder 1393)
    - Merrifield, No. 328, August 1963 (Box 217, Folder 1394)
    - Merrifield, No. 329, January 1964 (Box 217, Folder 1395)
    - Merrifield, No. 330, April 1965 (Box 217, Folder 1396)
    - Merrifield, No. 331, April 1966 (Box 217, Folder 1397)
    - Merrifield, No. 332, November 1967 (Box 218, Folder 1398)
    - Merrifield, No. 333, April 1968 (Box 218, Folder 1399)
    - Merrifield, No. 334, July 1990 (Box 218, Folder 1400)
    - Merrifield, No. 335, October 1991 (Box 218, Folder 1401)
    - Merrifield, No. 336, "Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis," October 1994 (Box 219, Folder 1402)
    - Merrifield, No. 337, August 1997 (Box 219, Folder 1403)
    - Merrifield, No. 338, September 1999 (Box 219, Folder 1404)
    - Merrifield, Notebook I, July 1949 (Box 219, Folder 1405)
    - Merrifield, Notebook II, February 1950 (Box 220, Folder 1406)
    - Merrifield, Notebook III, October 1950 (Box 220, Folder 1407)
    - Merrifield, E., No 1, "Synthesis of 1-66 IFN1," April 1980 (Box 220, Folder 1408)
    - Merrifield, E., No. 2, "Workup of Cys 1-166 IFN1," May 1981 (Box 221, Folder 1409)
    - Merrifield, E., No. 3, "Serine 1-166 Analog of IFN1," December 1981 (Box 221, Folder 1410)
    - Merrifield, E., No. 4, "2nd and 3rd Workups of Cys 1-166 IFN1," February 1982 (Box 221, Folder 1411)
    - "Methods" (Box 222, Folder 1412)
    - Methods (Box 222, Folder 1413)
    - Methods Folder (Box 222, Folder 1414)
    - M.G., No. 4, "Amino Acid Analyses, RSF," November 1971 (Box 222, Folder 1415)
    - M.G., No. 5, "A.A. Anal.," October 1972 (Box 222, Folder 1416)
    - M.G., No. 6, "A.A.A." (Box 222, Folder 1417)
    - Miscellaneous Data (Box 222, Folder 1418-1419)
    - Miscellaneous Data, 1975-1977 (Box 222, Folder 1420)
    - Miscellaneous Data and Old Drafts to Save (Box 223, Folder 1421)
    - Miscellaneous Material, 1966-1967 (Box 223, Folder 1422)
    - Miscellaneous Notes and Photos (Box 223, Folder 1423)
    - Mitchell, Scott, Lab Experiments (Box 223, Folder 1424-1426, Box 224, Folder 1427-1430, Box 225, Folder 1431-1433, Box 226, Folder 1434-1436)
    - Mitchell, No. 1, July 1989 (Box 226, Folder 1437)
    - Mitchell, No. 2, November 1989 (Box 227, Folder 1438)
    - Mitchell, No. 3, July 1990 (Box 227, Folder 1439)
    - Mitchell, No. 4, November 1990 (Box 227, Folder 1440)
    - Mitchell, No. 5, April 1991 (Box 227, Folder 1441)
    - Mitchell, No. 6, September 1991 (Box 227, Folder 1442)
    - Mitchell, No. 1A, "Amino Acid Analysis Information," April 1992 (Box 228, Folder 1443)
    - Model LAGV System (Box 228, Folder 1444)
    - Model Peptides (Box 228, Folder 1445)
    - Model Peptides Data and L.C. Values Table (Box 228, Folder 1446)
    - Mojsov, February-April (Box 228, Folder 1447)
    - Mojsov, April (Box 228, Folder 1448)
    - Mojsov, 1973 (Box 228, Folder 1449)
    - Mojsov, 1975-1976 (Box 229, Folder 1450)
    - Mojsov, 1980 (Box 229, Folder 1451)
    - Mojsov, 1981 (Box 229, Folder 1452)
    - Mojsov, 1981-1983 (Box 229, Folder 1453)
    - Mojsov, Binder, ASN Gly; Determination of Color Constants, Control Exp., 1978-1979 (Box 229, Folder 1454)
    - Mojsov, Binder, Boc Synthesis of Glucagon, 1981-1982 (Box 230, Folder 1455)
    - Mojsov, Binder, Influence of Strong Acids on Rehydration of Ala(CN)-Bly; Separation of Pyridine Acetate Column, 1976-1979 (Box 230, Folder 1456)
    - Mojsov, Binder, Synthesis of Asn-Gly (Bpoc) - Symmetrical Anhydride; -Ala(CN)-Gly; Iso-ASN-Gly; ASP-Gly Dipeptide, 1976-1979 (Box 230, Folder 1457)
    - Mojsov, Cleavage and Purification of Synthetic Glucagon Met Synthesis, Experiments Related to Oxidation Problem, 1983-1984 (Box 230, Folder 1458)
    - Mojsov, No. 1, Synthesis of Glucagon using Boc Met Experiments related to Oxidation, 1982-1983 (Box 231, Folder 1459)
    - Mojsov, No. 2, Synthesis of Glucagon using Boc Met(0), 1982-1983 (Box 231, Folder 1460)
    - Mojsov, Svetlana, Notes and Drafts, Glucagon (Box 231, Folder 1461)
    - "Monitor Charts", 1970 (Box 231, Folder 1462-1463)
    - Murphy, No. 1, December 1982 (Box 231, Folder 1464)
    - Muse, 1998-1999 (Box 232, Folder 1465)
    - "N-11-CB 62-74" (Box 232, Folder 1466)
    - Naayem, "Hydrolysis Analysis and CH2Cl2 Vesting," January 1981 (Box 232, Folder 1467)
    - Naayem, No. 1, January 1982 (Box 232, Folder 1468)
    - Naayem, No. 2, "Peptide Synthesis-Solid Phase," October 1982 (Box 232, Folder 1469)
    - Naayem, No. 3, March 1985 (Box 233, Folder 1470)
    - New Experiments (Box 233, Folder 1471)
    - New Experiments, Ideas, 1968-1970 (Box 233, Folder 1472)
    - New Glucagon Data, 1987 November 9 (Box 233, Folder 1473)
    - New Problems, Notes, Ideas, etc., 1974 (Box 233, Folder 1474)
    - New Research Problems and Experiments (Box 233, Folder 1475)
    - No. 1, "Amino Acid Analysis," March 1964 (Box 233, Folder 1476)
    - No. 1, "Bradykinin Assays," September 1963 (Box 234, Folder 1477)
    - No. 1, "Op. Dur. BPOC A.A.," RSF (Box 234, Folder 1478)
    - No. 2, November 1980 (Box 234, Folder 1479)
    - No. 2, "Amino Acid Analyses," July 1964 (Box 234, Folder 1480)
    - No. 2, "Peptide Syn.," April 1960 (Box 234, Folder 1481)
    - No. 3, "Peptides," December 1960 (Box 234, Folder 1482)
    - No. 4, "Peptides," June 1961 (Box 234, Folder 1483)
    - No. 5, "Peptides," November 1961 (Box 234, Folder 1484)
    - No. 6, "Peptides," November 1962 (Box 235, Folder 1485)
    - No. 7, "Peptides," August 1963 (Box 235, Folder 1486)
    - No. 8, "Peptides," February 1964 (Box 235, Folder 1487)
    - No. 9, "Peptides," November 1964 (Box 235, Folder 1488)
    - No. 10, "Peptides," January 1966 (Box 235, Folder 1489)
    - No. 11, "Peptides," October 1968 (Box 235, Folder 1490)
    - Notebook 340, Notes, Reprints, Old Data, Plans, etc. (Box 236, Folder 1491)
    - Notes and Data on New Experiments, 1974 (Box 236, Folder 1492)
    - Notes and Ideas, 1968-1969 (Box 236, Folder 1493)
    - Notes on My Chemistry Papers and General Notes, 1999 (Box 236, Folder 1494)
    - "Optical Purities," No. 2, June 1975 (Box 236, Folder 1495)
    - "Optical Purity Detns.," January 1975 (Box 237, Folder 1496)
    - Payne, June 1960 (Box 237, Folder 1497)
    - Phosphonomethylbenzyl Peptide NH2 and Binding to TiO2, 1992 (Box 237, Folder 1498)
    - Picrate Monitoring (Box 237, Folder 1499)
    - "Prosec," No. 1, 1985 (Box 237, Folder 1500)
    - "Prosec," No. 2, 1985 (Box 237, Folder 1501)
    - Protein Sequence Work (Box 238, Folder 1502)
    - Public Statements (Notes for Talks), 1983-1985 (Box 238, Folder 1503)
    - Racemization Experiments (Box 238, Folder 1504)
    - Radioactivity (Box 238, Folder 1505)
    - Ragnarsson, December 1969 (Box 238, Folder 1506)
    - Ray, No. 1, 1990 (Box 238, Folder 1507-1509)
    - Ray, No. 2, 1990 (Box 239, Folder 1510)
    - Research, Current (Box 239, Folder 1511)
    - Rethink Feb. '84 (SS and Overall Progress) (Box 239, Folder 1512)
    - Retro-enantio Data (Box 239, Folder 1513)
    - Retro-enantio Old Data (Box 239, Folder 1514)
    - Reverse Phase Silica Column (Box 239, Folder 1515)
    - RGD, TiO2, Libby and Bill (Box 239, Folder 1516)
    - Riemen, No. 16, August 1978 (Box 239, Folder 1517)
    - Riemen, No. 17, January 1979 (Box 239, Folder 1518)
    - Riemen, No. 18, May 1979 (Box 239, Folder 1519)
    - Riemen, No. 19, October 1979 (Box 240, Folder 1520)
    - RNase Activity, Assays (Box 240, Folder 1521)
    - RNase and AAA (Box 240, Folder 1522)
    - RNase, Blackburn and Moore (Box 240, Folder 1523)
    - RNase, Calculations, Notes, Ideas (Box 240, Folder 1524)
    - RNase, Hodges (Box 240, Folder 1525)
    - RNase Letters (Box 240, Folder 1526-1527)
    - RNase Substrate Literature (Box 241, Folder 1528)
    - RNase Substrate Synthesis (Box 241, Folder 1529)
    - RNase Summaries (Box 241, Folder 1530)
    - Rotondi, No. 1, April 1991 (Box 241, Folder 1531)
    - Rotondi, No. 2, December 1991 (Box 241, Folder 1532)
    - Rotondi, No. 3, June 1992 (Box 241, Folder 1533)
    - Rotondi, No. 4, 1993 (Box 242, Folder 1534)
    - Rotondi, No. 5, October 1993 (Box 242, Folder 1535)
    - Rotondi, No. 6, January 1994 (Box 242, Folder 1536)
    - Rotondi, No. 7, June 1994 (Box 242, Folder 1537)
    - Rotondi, No. 8, November 1994 (Box 242, Folder 1538)
    - Run 2 Complete, (Ala-Arg)(Ala-Arg)4, 1940 (Box 243, Folder 1539)
    - Run 7, 1970 (Box 243, Folder 1540)
    - Runs Recorded, 1970 (Box 243, Folder 1541)
    - Sadarangani, 1991-1992 (Box 243, Folder 1542-1543)
    - Sadarangani, No. 1, 1991 (Box 243, Folder 1544-1545)
    - Sarcotoxin (Li) (Box 243, Folder 1546)
    - Sarin, October 1982 (Box 244, Folder 1547)
    - Sarin, August 1983 (Box 244, Folder 1548)
    - Sarin, No. 6, September 1981 (Box 244, Folder 1549)
    - Seph G-25 Column to Desalt M45 (Box 244, Folder 1550)
    - Sequence Data, 1983-1984 (Box 244, Folder 1551)
    - Sequences - Truc. Receptors, 2004-2005 (Box 244, Folder 1552)
    - Sequencing on Sarin's Cys 1-155 IF2 (Box 244, Folder 1553)
    - Sharma, No. 1, August 1988 (Box 244, Folder 1544)
    - Sharma, No. 2, November 1988 (Box 244, Folder 1555)
    - Short CA-Me Hybrids (Box 244, Folder 1556)
    - Silveira (Box 244, Folder 1557)
    - Singer, No. 1, August 1985 (Box 245, Folder 1558)
    - Singer, No. 2, June 1986 (Box 245, Folder 1559)
    - Smatha...(illegible), June 2002 (Box 245, Folder 1560)
    - Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis General Plans and New Ideas, 1967-1968 (Box 245, Folder 1561)
    - Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis - Miscellaneous Data (Box 245, Folder 1562)
    - S- Peptide (Box 245, Folder 1563)
    - "SS Solubility, Antibody Columns" (Box 245, Folder 1564)
    - Stability of Boc-Thr (B21)-Pam-R (Box 245, Folder 1565)
    - Stanfield, "NMR," October 1963 (Box 245, Folder 1566)
    - Stewart, Book H, "High-Pressure Hydrogenation", 1953 (Box 245, Folder 1567)
    - Summary of Bpoc-AA-anh Experiments (Box 246, Folder 1568)
    - Supplemental Proceures, 1981-2003 (Box 246, Folder 1569)
    - Symmetrical Anh. Coupling (Box 246, Folder 1570)
    - Synthesis of ASN-Gly - Various Coupling Methods, 1978-1979 (Box 246, Folder 1571)
    - Synthesis of RNase Exptl (Box 246, Folder 1572)
    - Tauriello, "Lab Notes," May 1967 (Box 246, Folder 1573)
    - Tauriello, "Notebook 2," May 1968 (Box 247, Folder 1574)
    - Test Mixtures, Stds for Ala Arg, (Ala)2 Arg, (Ala)3 Arg, 1970 (Box 247, Folder 1570)
    - Test Peptide, [(Ala-Arg)4 Val], 1970 (Box 247, Folder 1576)
    - Things to Add to Summary or Notebook (Box 247, Folder 1577)
    - Total Hydrolysis and Trypsin Digests - Arg-Val, Ala-Arg-Val, Arg-Arg, 1970 (Box 247, Folder 1578)
    - Transposed Melittin Analogs (Box 247, Folder 1579)
    - Trypsin Inhibitor (Box 247, Folder 1580)
    - Trypsin Inhibitor Assays, Book I (Box 247, Folder 1581)
    - Uhrick, No. 3, July 1974 (Box 248, Folder 1582)
    - Unfoldered Materials, Assays, 1990 (Box 248, Folder 1583)
    - Unlabeled Binder (Box 248, Folder 1584-1585)
    - Unlabeled Folder (Box 248, Folder 1586-1590)
    - Unlabeled Folder, 1983 September 8 (Box 248, Folder 1591)
    - Unlabeled Folder, 1994 (Box 248, Folder 1592)
    - Unlabeled Folder, 1999 (Box 249, Folder 1593)
    - Unlabeled Notebook (Box 249, Folder 1594-1595)
    - Unlabeled Notes (Box 249, Folder 1596-1600, Box 250, Folder 1601)
    - Unlabeled Notes, 1984 (Box 250, Folder 1602)
    - Unlabeled Notes and Analyses (Box 250, Folder 1603)
    - Unson and Gurzenda, No. 1, 1987 (Box 250, Folder 1604)
    - Visarin, No. 2, October 1979 (Box 250, Folder 1605)
    - Vizioli, Lou, Plans (Box 250, Folder 1606)
    - Vizioli, "RNase," 1982 (Box 251, Folder 1607)
    - Vunnam, No. 1, 1993 (Box 251, Folder 1608)
    - Vunnam, No. 2, 1994 (Box 251, Folder 1609)
    - Vunnam, No. 3 (Box 251, Folder 1610)
    - Vunnam, No. 4 (Box 251, Folder 1611)
    - Vunnam, No 5 (Box 251, Folder 1612)
    - Vunnam, No. 6 (Box 252, Folder 1613)
    - Vunnam, No. 7 (Box 252, Folder 1614)
    - Vunnam, No. 8 (Box 252, Folder 1615)
    - Whitney, No. 2, January 1982 (Box 252, Folder 1616)
    - Whitney, No. 3, June 1982 (Box 252, Folder 1617)
    - Whitney, No. 4, October 1982 (Box 252, Folder 1618)
    - Whitney, No. 5, January 1983 (Box 253, Folder 1619)
    - Whitney, No. 6, June 1983 (Box 253, Folder 1620)
    - Whitney, No 7, November 1983 (Box 253, Folder 1621)
    - Whitney, No. 8, February 1984 (Box 253, Folder 1622)
    - Wong, "Bioassay Record", 1979 (Box 253, Folder 1623)
    - Wong, No. 3, March 1979 (Box 254, Folder 1624)
    - Wong, No. 4, 1979 (Box 254, Folder 1625)
    - Wong, Record Book No. 1, August 1978 (Box 254, Folder 1626)
    - "Workup of Sarin's Serine 1-155 IF2 Peptide", 1983 August (Box 254, Folder 1627)
    - Wu, Antibody, 1994-1995 (Box 255, Folder 1628)
    - Wu, "Boc-D-AA Derivatives", 1975 (Box 255, Folder 1629)
    - Wu, "Boc-D-AA Derivatives", 1976 April (Box 255, Folder 1630)
    - Wu, "Competitive Assays", 1992-1997 (Box 255, Folder 1631)
    - Wu, "Experimental Procedures and Results", 1974 September (Box 255, Folder 1632)
    - Wu, No. 1, June 1975 (Box 255, Folder 1633)
    - Wu, No. 1, 1993 (Box 256, Folder 1634)
    - Wu, No. 1, Binding Assays, 1992-1993 (Box 256, Folder 1635)
    - Wu, No. 1, COS-cell and Membrane, 1994-1996 (Box 256, Folder 1636)
    - Wu, No. 1, Regular Assays, 1992-1994 (Box 256, Folder 1637)
    - Wu, No. 2, July 1975 (Box 257, Folder 1638)
    - Wu, No. 2, Binding Assays, 1993-2000 (Box 257, Folder 1639)
    - Wu, No. 2, Cos-Cell and Membrane, 1996 (Box 257, Folder 1640)
    - Wu, No. 2, Regular Assays, 1995-1999 (Box 257, Folder 1641)
    - Wu, No. 3, September 1975 (Box 257, Folder 1642)
    - Wu, No. 3, Cos-cell and Membrane, 1996-1997 (Box 258, Folder 1643)
    - Wu, No. 4, January 1976 (Box 258, Folder 1644)
    - Wu, No. 4, Cos-cell and Membrane, 1997-1998 (Box 258, Folder 1645)
    - Wu, No. 5, April 1976 (Box 258, Folder 1646)
    - Wu, No. 5, Cos-cell Membrane, 1998-1999 (Box 259, Folder 1647)
    - Wu, No. 6, June 1976 (Box 259, Folder 1648)
    - Wu, "Synthesis for Project I", 1976 (Box 259, Folder 1649)
    - Wu/Kent, "Amino Acid Analyses of Commercial D-Amino Acids", 1975 February (Box 259, Folder 1650)
    - Yang (Box 259, Folder 1651)
    - Yang, Binder, H(FIXC-EGF), Lab Notes, Computer Handouts, 1989-1993 (Box 259, Folder 1652)
    - Yang, Binder, L(FIXC-EGF), 1992-1993 (Box 260, Folder 1653-1654)
    - Yang, Binder, L(FIXC-EGF), Refolding, Rx 53-87, 1992 (Box 260, Folder 1655-1656)
    - Yang, Binder, L(FIXC-EGF), Synthesis Small Scale Trials Mass Z-nzyme Digestion, 1992-1993 (Box 260, Folder 1657, Box 261, Folder 1658)
    - Yang, Binder, L(FIXC-EGF) (Rx 1-24), 1992-1993 (Box 261, Folder 1659)
    - Yang, Binder, Notes about H, 1991-1995 (Box 261, Folder 1660, Box 262, Folder 1661)
    - Yang, Binder, T, 1993-1994 (Box 262, Folder 1662-1663)
    - Yoo, 1993-1997 (Box 262, Folder 1664-1665)
    - Yoo, Barney, Binder (Box 263, Folder 1666)
    - Yoo, Barney, Binder, 1997-1998 (Box 263, Folder 1667)
    - Yoo, Barney, Lab Experiments (Box 263, Folder 1668-1669, Box 264, Folder 1670)
    - Yoo, No. 1, 1993-1994 (Box 264, Folder 1671)
    - Yoo, No. 3, 1994 (Box 264, Folder 1672)
    - Yoo, No. 4, 1994-1996 (Box 264, Folder 1673)
    - Yoo, No. 5, 1996-1997 (Box 264, Folder 1674)
    - Yoo, No. 6, 1997-1998 (Box 265, Folder 1675)
    - Yoo, No. 7, 1998 (Box 265, Folder 1676)
    - Yoshida, No. 1, 1991 (Box 265, Folder 1677)
    - Yoshida, No. 2, 1992 (Box 265, Folder 1678)
    - Yoshida, No. 3, 1992 (Box 265, Folder 1679)
    - Yoshida and E. Merrifield, 1992 (Box 265, Folder 1680)
- Manuscripts and Publications, 5
  - #1, 1947 (Box 266, Folder 1681)
  - #2, 1948 (Box 266, Folder 1682)
  - #3, 1949 (Box 266, Folder 1683)
  - #4, 1950 (Box 266, Folder 1684)
  - #5-#8, 1952 (Box 266, Folder 1685)
  - #9-#10, 1954 (Box 266, Folder 1686)
  - #11-#12, 1955 (Box 266, Folder 1687)
  - #13-#14, 1956 (Box 266, Folder 1688)
  - #15-#18, 1958 (Box 266, Folder 1689)
  - #19-#20, 1962 (Box 266, Folder 1690)
  - #21, 1963 (Box 266, Folder 1691)
  - #22-#24, 1964 (Box 266, Folder 1692)
  - #25-#28, 1965 (Box 266, Folder 1693)
  - #29-#32, 1966 (Box 266, Folder 1694)
  - #33-#36, 1967 (Box 266, Folder 1695)
  - #37-#40, 1968 (Box 266, Folder 1696)
  - #43-#51, 1969 (Box 266, Folder 1697)
  - #53-#56, 1970 (Box 266, Folder 1698)
  - #57-#62, 1971 (Box 266, Folder 1699)
  - #65-#73, 1972 (Box 266, Folder 1700)
  - #74-#80, 1973 (Box 267, Folder 1701)
  - #81-#85, 1973 (Box 267, Folder 1702)
  - #86-#89, 1974 (Box 267, Folder 1703)
  - #90-#91, 1975 (Box 267, Folder 1704)
  - #92, 1975 (Box 268, Folder 1705)
  - #93-#94, 1975 (Box 268, Folder 1706)
  - #95-#98, 1975 (Box 268, Folder 1707)
  - #102-#103, 1976 (Box 268, Folder 1708)
  - #104-#105, 1976 (Box 268, Folder 1709)
  - #106, 1976 (Box 269, Folder 1710)
  - #107-#109, 1976 (Box 269, Folder 1711)
  - #110, 1976 (Box 269, Folder 1712)
  - #111-#112, 1977 (Box 269, Folder 1713)
  - #113, 1977 (Box 269, Folder 1714)
  - #114-#115, 1977 (Box 270, Folder 1715)
  - #116-#118, 1977 (Box 270, Folder 1716)
  - #119-#120, 1977 (Box 270, Folder 1717)
  - #121, 1978 (Box 270, Folder 1718)
  - #122-#123, 1978 (Box 270, Folder 1719)
  - #124, 1978 (Box 270, Folder 1720)
  - #126, 1978 (Box 271, Folder 1721)
  - #127, 1978 (Box 271, Folder 1722)
  - #128-#129, 1979 (Box 271, Folder 1723)
  - #130, 1979 (Box 271, Folder 1724)
  - #131-#133, 1979 (Box 271, Folder 1725)
  - #133-#137, 1979 (Box 271, Folder 1726)
  - #138-#139, 1979 (Box 272, Folder 1727)
  - #140-#142, 1979 (Box 272, Folder 1728)
  - #143, 1979 (Box 272, Folder 1729)
  - #144, 1980 (Box 272, Folder 1730)
  - #145, 1980 (Box 272, Folder 1731)
  - #146, 1980 (Box 273, Folder 1732)
  - #147-#149, 1980 (Box 273, Folder 1733)
  - #150, 1981 (Box 273, Folder 1734)
  - #151-#154, 1981 (Box 273, Folder 1735)
  - #155-#156, 1981 (Box 273, Folder 1736)
  - #157, 1981 (Box 274, Folder 1737)
  - #158-#159, 1981 (Box 274, Folder 1738)
  - #161-#163, 1982 (Box 274, Folder 1739)
  - #164-#167, 1983 (Box 274, Folder 1741)
  - #171, 1983 (Box 275, Folder 1742)
  - #172-#174, 1983 (Box 275, Folder 1743)
  - #175-#176, 1983 (Box 275, Folder 1744)
  - #177-#183, 1983 (Box 275, Folder 1745)
  - #184-#185, 1984 (Box 275, Folder 1746)
  - #186, 1985 (Box 275, Folder 1747)
  - #187-#191, 1984-1985 (Box 276, Folder 1748)
  - #192-#193, 1984 (Box 276, Folder 1749)
  - #194-#202, 1984-1987 (Box 276, Folder 1750)
  - #203-#205, 1985-1986 (Box 276, Folder 1751)
  - #206-#207, 1986-1987 (Box 277, Folder 1752)
  - #208-#214, 1986 (Box 277, Folder 1753)
  - #215-#217, 1986 (Box 277, Folder 1754)
  - #218-#219, 1987 (Box 277, Folder 1755)
  - #220-#222, 1986-1987 (Box 278, Folder 1756)
  - #223-#224, 1987 (Box 278, Folder 1757)
  - #225-#226, 1987-1988 (Box 278, Folder 1758)
  - #226-#230, 1987-1988 (Box 278, Folder 1759)
  - #231-#232, 1987; 1989 (Box 279, Folder 1760)
  - #233-#234, 1988 (Box 279, Folder 1761)
  - #235-#238, 1988 (Box 279, Folder 1762)
  - #238-#240, 1988 (Box 279, Folder 1763)
  - #241-#243, 1989 (Box 280, Folder 1764)
  - #244, 1989 (Box 280, Folder 1765)
  - #244, #246, #252 (Box 280, Folder 1766)
  - #245-#246, 1989 (Box 280, Folder 1767)
  - #247-#249, 1988-1989 (Box 280, Folder 1768)
  - #250 (Box 281, Folder 1769)
  - #251-#252, 1989 (Box 281, Folder 1770)
  - #253, 1991 (Box 281, Folder 1771)
  - #254 A (Box 282, Folder 1772)
  - #254 B (Box 282, Folder 1773)
  - #256-#257, 1990 (Box 282, Folder 1774)
  - #259-#261, 1990-1991 (Box 282, Folder 1775)
  - #262-#268, 1990-1992 (Box 283, Folder 1776)
  - #269-#270 (Box 283, Folder 1777)
  - #271-#272, 1992 (Box 283, Folder 1778)
  - #274-#276, 1993-1994 (Box 283, Folder 1779)
  - #277-#285, 1992-1995 (Box 284, Folder 1780)
  - #286-#294, 1994 (Box 284, Folder 1781)
  - #295, 1995 (Box 284, Folder 1782)
  - #296-#298, 1994-1996 (Box 284, Folder 1783)
  - #299 (Box 285, Folder 1784)
  - #300 (Box 285, Folder 1785)
  - #303, 1997 (Box 285, Folder 1786)
  - #304, 1995 (Box 285, Folder 1787)
  - #306, 1996 (Box 285, Folder 1788)
  - #307, 1996 (Box 285, Folder 1789)
  - #308, 1996 (Box 286, Folder 1790)
  - #309, 1997 (Box 286, Folder 1791)
  - #310, 1997 (Box 286, Folder 1792)
  - #311, 1997 (Box 286, Folder 1793)
  - #312-#317 (Box 286, Folder 1794)
  - #318-#319 (Box 287, Folder 1795)
  - #322 (Box 287, Folder 1796)
    - The Journal of Peptide Research: Structure activity... melittin hybrids, 2016:FA415:006 (Box 287, Folder 1796)
    - MS Word 5.1 for Macintosh - Retro/RBM, 2016:FA415:020 (Box 287)
  - #323 (Box 287, Folder 1797)
  - #324, 1999 (Box 287, Folder 1798)
  - #325 (Box 287, Folder 1799)
  - #326 (Box 287, Folder 1800)
  - #328, 2001 (Box 287, Folder 1801)
  - #329, 1999 (Box 287, Folder 1802)
  - #323, 2000 (Box 287, Folder 1803, Box 288, Folder 1804)
  - #330 (Box 288, Folder 1805)
  - #330a-e (Box 288, Folder 1806-1810)
    - Molecular Clocks - Robinson, NE and Robinson AB Computer Disk, 2016:FA415:007 (Box 288, Folder 1807)
  - "I. Synthesis and Photochemical Addition Reactions of Compounds Related to a 3-Carbethoxycyclohexenone, II. Photochemical Cyclization of 5-Hexenal" by Lowrance, 1970 (Box 288, Folder 1811)
  - "13C and 15N Nuclear Magnetic Resonance Studies on Amino Acids and Peptides" by Sogn, 1973 (Box 288, Folder 1812)
  - [14C] DCC (Dicyclohexylcarbodiimide) (Box 289, Folder 1813)
  - 1970 Yearbook, McGraw-Hill (Box 289, Folder 1814)
  - "The -Phenacyl Ester as a Temporary Protecting Group to Minimize Cyclic Imide Formation during Subsequent Treatment of Aspartyl Peptides with HF1,2" by Yang and Merrifield (Box 289, Folder 1815)
  - Abstracts, 2nd American Peptide Symposium (Box 289, Folder 1816)
  - Abstracts Not Presented at 3rd American Peptide Symposium (Box 289, Folder 1817)
  - "Active-Site Structure and Substrate Recognition in Protein Kinases" by Miller, 1988 (Box 289, Folder 1818)
  - Adv. Enzymol. 1969 ("Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis" by Merrifield) (Box 289, Folder 1818)
  - Alewood (Box 289, Folder 1820)
  - Alewood (Box 289, Folder 1820A)
  - All In Final Write-Up, 2003 (Box 290, Folder 1821)
  - Andreu, Discontinuous Antigens (Box 290, Folder 1822)
  - Andreu, PNAS (Box 290, Folder 1823)
  - Andreu, PNAS (Box 290, Folder 1823A)
  - Angiotensin #235 and #242. Copies of HPLC (Box 290, Folder 1824)
  - Annual Review of Biochemistry (Box 290, Folder 1825)
  - Antibacterial Peptides (Box 290, Folder 1826)
  - Apamin (Box 290, Folder 1827)
  - Apparatus for the Automated Synthesis of Peptides (Box 291, Folder 1828)
  - Articles Used in SPPS (Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis) Chapter, Gutte (Box 291, Folder 1829-1832)
  - Automated Peptide Synthesis (Box 291, Folder 1833)
  - Automated Synthesis of Peptides (Box 292, Folder 1834-1835)